### Contact

liz.david2000@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-david-0472261b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Hospitals
Nursing
Healthcare Management

# Elizabeth David

#### **CNO**

Thane

# Summary

A Nursing professional with over 20 years of experience at all levels of nursing with a Master's Degree in Nursing and a Hospital Administration Diploma (TISS). Presently working as the Chief Nursing Officer (CNO) at the Sir H N Reliance Foundation Hospital, Mumbai.

# Experience

Sir H.N Reliance Foundation Hospital Chief Nursing Officer March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Valiance Healthcare
V. P - Nursing and Quality
February 2018 - February 2019 (1 year 1 month)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Sir H.N Reliance Foundation Hospital and Research Center Head - Clinical Nursing and Operations January 2014 - November 2017 (3 years 11 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Global Hospital
Chief - Nursing Services
November 2012 - January 2014 (1 year 3 months)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Kohinoor Hospital Chief - Nursing Services November 2010 - November 2012 (2 years 1 month) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Kokilaben Dhirubhai Ambani Hospital Assistant General manager

#### January 2010 - November 2010 (11 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Bion Healthcare LLC
Chief - Nursing Services
April 2004 - April 2010 (6 years 1 month)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Asian Heart Institute and Research Center Manager - Nursing (Critical Care Units) April 2002 - April 2004 (2 years 1 month)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Hinduja Hospital Lecturer June 2000 - January 2002 (1 year 8 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

## LILAVATI HOSPITAL AND RESEARCH CENTRE

Staff Nurse - ICU May 1996 - May 1998 (2 years 1 month) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

## Education

L.T College of Nursing BSN & MSN, Nursing · (1992 - 2000)

JJTU Ph.D · (2018 - 2022)

Tata Institute of Social Sciences

Executive Post Graduate Fiploma in Hospital Administration, Health/Health Care Administration/Management · (2016 - 2017)